{
  "total_posts": 139,
  "categories": {
    "ingredient_usage_patterns": [
      {
        "post_id": "zas7a5",
        "title": "[Anti-Aging] I may have used too much retinol and sunscreen. Maybe I should add some biotin for my thinning hair?",
        "clean_title": "I may have used too much retinol and sunscreen. Maybe I should add some biotin for my thinning hair?",
        "subreddit": "SkincareAddiction",
        "score": 16149,
        "num_comments": 116,
        "created": "2022-12-02T17:36:48+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "retinol",
          "biotin",
          "sunscreen"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "retinol",
          "biotin",
          "sunscreen"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "sunscreen"
        ],
        "entities": [],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "9 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "SCAcirclejerk",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Nah",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Love",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
          ],
          [
            "Omg",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Drop",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Grade A",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Drop",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "glowup",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Baby Shark",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Order of the Phoenix",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "a Death Eater's",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": false,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 7,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 2,
          "negative": 1
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 1
      },
      {
        "post_id": "12wkj52",
        "title": "Almost 1 year post op ….haven’t had this much hair since I was 18….regimen…topical fin/min viviscal…biotin…sulfate free shampoo/nizoral 3 times a week",
        "clean_title": "Almost 1 year post op ….haven’t had this much hair since I was 18….regimen…topical fin/min viviscal…biotin…sulfate free shampoo/nizoral 3 times a week",
        "subreddit": "tressless",
        "score": 357,
        "num_comments": 164,
        "created": "2023-04-23T18:11:09+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "minoxidil",
          "fin",
          "nizoral",
          "min"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "fin",
          "nizoral",
          "biotin",
          "min"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "fin",
          "minoxidil",
          "min"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "Almost 1 year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "18",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Congrats",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "43",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "December",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "about 4 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the next few months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Serkan Aygin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Turkey",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "40+",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "40+",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Hims My",
            "PRODUCT"
          ],
          [
            "6",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Turkey",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "America",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Michigan",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "the morning",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "Hair",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "2",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "2",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "😆",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "5-6 month",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "🤫🤫 4",
            "PRODUCT"
          ],
          [
            "Motrin",
            "LOC"
          ],
          [
            "🙏",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "3100",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "100",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            ".200",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "10 years ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Turkey",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Serkan Aygin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "3100",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "every penny",
            "MONEY"
          ],
          [
            "Good",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": false,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 7,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 3,
          "negative": 1
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 5
      },
      {
        "post_id": "i20nt7",
        "title": "My results of about 6 months of minoxidil + head massages + biotin + all around taking care of my body and hair.",
        "clean_title": "My results of about 6 months of minoxidil + head massages + biotin + all around taking care of my body and hair.",
        "subreddit": "tressless",
        "score": 339,
        "num_comments": 87,
        "created": "2020-08-01T21:56:40+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "keto",
          "biotin",
          "finasteride",
          "fin",
          "vitamins",
          "min"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "keto",
          "biotin",
          "finasteride",
          "fin",
          "vitamins",
          "min"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "about 6 months",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Fin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Fin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "a few months/years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "million",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "50%",
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "30 days",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "every single day",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "5000",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "mcg tablet",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "10000",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "MPB",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "2-3 minutes",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "5",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "three weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "the next few days",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "night",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "Fin about 3 week's",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "about 5 years ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "30 days",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "about 0.25",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1mg/week",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Norwood 3/3.5",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "fin & Keto(2%",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "a week",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "0.5",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "0.25",
            "CARDINAL"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 10,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 5,
          "negative": 4
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "5000",
            "mcg"
          ],
          [
            "10000",
            "mcg"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "0.25",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "0.5",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "0.25",
            "mg"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 8
      },
      {
        "post_id": "1ede7fl",
        "title": "10.5 months. Oral propecia, topical minoxidil (once daily) derma roller. And for the last two (2) months, I've been doing the bald showers after leg workouts... Biotin and Omega 3 age 35. Loses a lot of hair a day, over 150",
        "clean_title": "10.5 months. Oral propecia, topical minoxidil (once daily) derma roller. And for the last two (2) months, I've been doing the bald showers after leg workouts... Biotin and Omega 3 age 35. Loses a lot of hair a day, over 150",
        "subreddit": "tressless",
        "score": 242,
        "num_comments": 137,
        "created": "2024-07-27T11:29:05+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "derma roll",
          "minoxidil",
          "derma roller",
          "fin",
          "biotin",
          "dermarolling",
          "omega",
          "min"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "omega",
          "minoxidil",
          "derma roller",
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "dermarolling",
          "derma roll",
          "derma roller",
          "minoxidil",
          "fin",
          "min"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "10.5 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the last two (2) months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "age 35",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "over 150",
            "CARDINAL"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "1mg a day",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "35 years old",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the age of",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "70",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "22 hours",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "Probably",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "1.5",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1.5",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "a week",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Friday",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "3/10",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "a hour",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "every day",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "cold\\*\\*\\",
            "ORG"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 10,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 2,
          "negative": 4
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 3
      },
      {
        "post_id": "1g0vy9u",
        "title": "Oral Biotin and Topical Minoxidil have a synergy effect in increasing hair growth, the study was only done in healthy subjects and it was only 14 days but it does prove that biotin can play a significant role as an adjunct treatment.",
        "clean_title": "Oral Biotin and Topical Minoxidil have a synergy effect in increasing hair growth, the study was only done in healthy subjects and it was only 14 days but it does prove that biotin can play a significant role as an adjunct treatment.",
        "subreddit": "tressless",
        "score": 169,
        "num_comments": 41,
        "created": "2024-10-10T23:13:16+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "vitamin ",
          "vitamin b",
          "biotin",
          "finasteride",
          "fin",
          "vitamins",
          "min"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "vitamin ",
          "vitamin b",
          "biotin",
          "finasteride",
          "fin",
          "vitamins",
          "min"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "only 14 days",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "weekly",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Creedence",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Ten",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "AGA",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "First",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "AGA",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "AGA",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "MPB",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "5",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "5000",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "YouTube",
            "PRODUCT"
          ],
          [
            "about 0.2 inches",
            "QUANTITY"
          ],
          [
            "0.5 inches",
            "QUANTITY"
          ],
          [
            "about 10 seconds",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "night",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "3-5 days",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the end of the day",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "3x",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "10,000",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "b5 increase",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "B6",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Creatine",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Creatine",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "10,000",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "mcg dose",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "only 5,000",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "mcg",
            "ORG"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": false,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 9,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 3,
          "negative": 2
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [
          [
            "5",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "5000",
            "mcg"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "000",
            "mcg"
          ],
          [
            "000",
            "mcg"
          ],
          [
            "000",
            "mcg"
          ],
          [
            "5",
            "mg"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 6
      },
      {
        "post_id": "41wk6n",
        "title": "38 MTF Hair Regrowth on Spiro, Fin, E and Biotin - 10 month difference",
        "clean_title": "38 MTF Hair Regrowth on Spiro, Fin, E and Biotin - 10 month difference",
        "subreddit": "transtimelines",
        "score": 161,
        "num_comments": 30,
        "created": "2016-01-20T21:46:48+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "finasteride",
          "fin"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "fin",
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "fin",
          "biotin",
          "finasteride"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "38",
            "CARDINAL"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "39",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Finasteride",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "29 mtf",
            "QUANTITY"
          ],
          [
            "pre-hrt",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "a week",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "every day",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "every two weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "today",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "about month 5",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "HRT",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Costco",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "two minutes",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "Sorry Congratulations",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Fin/Spiro",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "about two weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "23",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "DHT",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "about 3 years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "100",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Spiro",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "almost a month ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Fin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Finasteride",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "5 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "4",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "bell pepper",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "over 40",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "the last 6 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "five",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Finesteride",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Congrats",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "45",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Congrats",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Glad",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 9,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 7,
          "negative": 1
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [
          [
            "100",
            "mg"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 4
      },
      {
        "post_id": "jk1jwg",
        "title": "I need science to fix this. Frizz, breaking, baby hairs coming in, hair loss, wirey. Im taking biotin and all other nutrients I need (omegas, protein) according to a blood and DNA test. Any advice?",
        "clean_title": "I need science to fix this. Frizz, breaking, baby hairs coming in, hair loss, wirey. Im taking biotin and all other nutrients I need (omegas, protein) according to a blood and DNA test. Any advice?",
        "subreddit": "HaircareScience",
        "score": 150,
        "num_comments": 69,
        "created": "2020-10-29T02:06:34+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "iron",
          "biotin"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "iron"
        ],
        "entities": [],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Mell",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "YouTube",
            "PRODUCT"
          ],
          [
            "Cantu",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "SheaMoisture Coconut",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Hibiscus",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Kinky-Curly",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "hours",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "days",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "all day",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "2 years ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "daily",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "daily",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "daily",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "every day",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Kerastese",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "100%",
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Jessicurl",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Maui",
            "LOC"
          ],
          [
            "Eva NYC",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "10",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "2-3 weeks",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 9,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 4,
          "negative": 3
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 5
      },
      {
        "post_id": "1fxl992",
        "title": "4 Month .. 3500 grafts Now Hair Time, Istanbul No fin no min , just biotin and 2 PRP session!",
        "clean_title": "4 Month .. 3500 grafts Now Hair Time, Istanbul No fin no min , just biotin and 2 PRP session!",
        "subreddit": "HairTransplants",
        "score": 106,
        "num_comments": 83,
        "created": "2024-10-06T17:03:23+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "minoxidil",
          "finasteride",
          "fin",
          "min"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "fin",
          "biotin",
          "min"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "fin",
          "minoxidil",
          "min",
          "finasteride"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "4 Month",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "3500",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Istanbul",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "2",
            "CARDINAL"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "80",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "80",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "🤣 Looks",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "last week",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "3400",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "zero",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1-3 weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "1-3 weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "2022",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "2 weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "12 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "13 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Today",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "5 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "SECOND",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "5 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Minoxidl",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "1 month",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "5 days ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the next 8 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Hair",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "a few years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "45 year old",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "second",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "6k",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "2500-3000",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1500",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1500",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "5,000",
            "CARDINAL"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 10,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 3,
          "negative": 5
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1.1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "5",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "5",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1.1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "2.5",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1.1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1.1",
            "mg"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 6
      },
      {
        "post_id": "t89mej",
        "title": "A meta analysis of 18 popular hair loss treatments. An 2022 guide on efficacy. From finasteride and minoxidil to caffeine shampoo, saw palmetto and biotin. 96 Scientific References included.",
        "clean_title": "A meta analysis of 18 popular hair loss treatments. An 2022 guide on efficacy. From finasteride and minoxidil to caffeine shampoo, saw palmetto and biotin. 96 Scientific References included.",
        "subreddit": "tressless",
        "score": 103,
        "num_comments": 39,
        "created": "2022-03-06T22:01:22+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "finasteride",
          "dermarolling",
          "minoxidil",
          "zinc"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "biotin",
          "finasteride"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "zinc",
          "minoxidil",
          "finasteride",
          "dermarolling"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "18",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "2022",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "96",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Scientific References",
            "ORG"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Meta",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Meta",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "about 66%",
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            "Bibliography",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Mella",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "J. M., Perret",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Manzotti",
            "LOC"
          ],
          [
            "H. N.,",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "G.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "2010",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "146(10",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "1141-1150",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "2",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Male Pattern",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "2002",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "5-year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "European Journal of Dermatology",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "12(1",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "38",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "J., & Kaufman",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "2003, June",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Journal of Investigative Dermatology Symposium Proceedings",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "8",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "pp",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "20-23",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "4",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Olsen",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Hordinsky",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "D.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Stough",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "D.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Hobbs",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "S., Ellis",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "M. L.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "2006",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "5α",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "the American Academy of Dermatology",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "55(6",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1014-1023",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "5",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Kaufman",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "K. D.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Olsen",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "D.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Savin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "R.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "DeVillez",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "R.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Bergfeld",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "W.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "1998",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the American Academy of Dermatology",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "39(4",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "578",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "6",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "D. B.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "KAUFMAN",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "K. D.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "2002",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "European Journal of Dermatology",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "12(1",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "32",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "7",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Gupta",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "A. K.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Venkataraman",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "M.",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Talukder",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "M., & Bamimore",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "2021",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Journal of Dermatological Treatment",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "8",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Olszewska",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "M., & Rudnicka",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "L.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "2005",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "JDD",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "4(5",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "637",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "9",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Tsunemi",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Y.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Irisawa",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "R.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Yoshiie",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Brotherton",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Tsuboi",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "R.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "2016",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Journal",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "1051-1058",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "10",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Olsen",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Hordinsky",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "D.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Stough",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "D.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Hobbs",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "S., Ellis",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "M. L.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "2006",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "5α",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "the American Academy of Dermatology",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "55(6",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1014-1023",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "11",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Eun",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "H. C.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "O. S.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Yeon",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "J. H.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Shin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "H. S.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Kim",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "B. Y.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "2010",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "0.5",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "the American Academy of Dermatology",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "63(2",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "252",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "12",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "D.",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "2007",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "6(1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "9",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Chicago",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "13",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Olsen",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Weiner",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "M. S.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Amara",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "I. A.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "E. R.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "1990",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Five-year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the American Academy of Dermatology",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "22(4",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "643",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "14",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Fiedler-Weiss",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "V. C.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "1987",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "1% and 5%",
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            "the American Academy of Dermatology",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "16(3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "745",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "15",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "2019",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "13, 2777",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "16",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Messenger",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "A. G.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "J.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "2004",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "British",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "150(2",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "186",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "17",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "A. W.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Piacquadio",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Ditre",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "C. M.,",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Dunlap",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "I.",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "A. G.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "2004",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "5% and",
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            "2%",
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            "the American Academy of Dermatology",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "50(4",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "541",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Chicago",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "18",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "DeVillez",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "R. L.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Jacobs",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "J. P.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Szpunar",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "C. A.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "M. L.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "1994",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "2%",
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            "130(3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "303",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "19",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Sultan C",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Devillier C",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Briley M",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Descomps B. Inhibition",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Serenoa",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "20",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Ellis JA",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Harrap SB",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": false,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 9,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 4,
          "negative": 4
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "0.5",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "5600",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "560",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "1800",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "320",
            "mg"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 8
      },
      {
        "post_id": "1kenh3m",
        "title": "Biohacks for good skin and hair? Please don’t say biotin.",
        "clean_title": "Biohacks for good skin and hair? Please don’t say biotin.",
        "subreddit": "Biohackers",
        "score": 98,
        "num_comments": 181,
        "created": "2025-05-04T16:10:49+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "retinol",
          "vitamin c",
          "microneedling",
          "zinc",
          "vitamin d",
          "biotin",
          "sunscreen",
          "omega"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "retinol",
          "vitamin c",
          "microneedling",
          "zinc",
          "vitamin d",
          "biotin",
          "sunscreen",
          "omega"
        ],
        "entities": [],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Morning",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "Red",
            "PRODUCT"
          ],
          [
            "Collagen",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "C Red",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "night",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "the day",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "7-8 hours",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "a week",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "24+ hours",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "Second",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Metformin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "the past two years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "4",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Smoothies",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "NAG\n\nHyaluronic",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "B5",
            "PRODUCT"
          ],
          [
            "Collagen",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "HGH",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "GHK-Cu",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "between 1000-2000",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Hooga HG300",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "200",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "5",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "daily",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "about 4-5x",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "a week",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "early afternoon",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "Niacinimide Collagen",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": false,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": false,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 8,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 3,
          "negative": 0
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [
          [
            "4",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "12",
            "mg"
          ],
          [
            "2000",
            "mg"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 2
      },
      {
        "post_id": "y4b2tt",
        "title": "I haven't cut/trimmed my hair in about 6 years. I want it to grow longer without having to trim it. Can I with biotin or something?",
        "clean_title": "I haven't cut/trimmed my hair in about 6 years. I want it to grow longer without having to trim it. Can I with biotin or something?",
        "subreddit": "longhair",
        "score": 95,
        "num_comments": 23,
        "created": "2022-10-15T01:31:07+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "vitamin d3",
          "vitamin c",
          "iron",
          "zinc",
          "biotin",
          "omega",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "vitamin d3",
          "vitamin c",
          "iron",
          "zinc",
          "biotin",
          "omega",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "about 6 years",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "daily",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "n’t",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Coconut Oil",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "a years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Coconut Oil",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Miracle Oil",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "winter",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "every few days",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "actualy",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "daily",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "cassia",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "2 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Cassia",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Georgie Mane",
            "FAC"
          ],
          [
            "about 4 months ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "a week",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Georgie Mane",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Mane and Tail",
            "WORK_OF_ART"
          ],
          [
            "Coconut Oil",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "a few years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Coconut Oil",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Miracle Oil",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "22",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Brock",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 9,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 9,
          "negative": 2
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 7
      },
      {
        "post_id": "z0popx",
        "title": "All in restoration Hair transplant from Dr Serkan in Turkey + topical fin/min Viviscal,biotin,sulfate free shampoo and Nizoral…very happy with results",
        "clean_title": "All in restoration Hair transplant from Dr Serkan in Turkey + topical fin/min Viviscal,biotin,sulfate free shampoo and Nizoral…very happy with results",
        "subreddit": "tressless",
        "score": 92,
        "num_comments": 82,
        "created": "2022-11-21T04:43:43+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "fin",
          "nizoral",
          "min"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "fin",
          "nizoral",
          "biotin",
          "min"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "fin",
          "min"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "Serkan",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Turkey",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Nizoral",
            "ORG"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "3100",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Serkan Aygen",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Europe",
            "LOC"
          ],
          [
            "4",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "2800",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "100",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "200",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "10 years ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "don’t",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Serkan Aygin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "5",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Europe",
            "LOC"
          ],
          [
            "3100",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Turkey",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Hair",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Serkan Aygin + 2019",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "10",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Turkey",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "2800",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "1800",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Florida",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "15k",
            "MONEY"
          ],
          [
            "Turkey",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "3100",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "3100",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "3100",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "2",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Istanbul",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "3 weeks ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "States",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Istanbul",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Canada",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "18",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "27-29",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "4810",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Canada",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Serkan",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "California",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Europe",
            "LOC"
          ],
          [
            "3100",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "well over half",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC6371726/",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "the first months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "10 years ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "a 5 years ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "first few months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "mark wahlberg",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "3 weeks ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "US",
            "GPE"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 8,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 6,
          "negative": 2
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 6
      },
      {
        "post_id": "11xfnk7",
        "title": "This is your reminder: Take your vitamins. Take your biotin. Your hair will grow back. You a beautiful and strong.",
        "clean_title": "This is your reminder: Take your vitamins. Take your biotin. Your hair will grow back. You a beautiful and strong.",
        "subreddit": "BariatricSurgery",
        "score": 91,
        "num_comments": 28,
        "created": "2023-03-21T12:39:39+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "vitamin ",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "vitamin ",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "entities": [],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "5 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "4 years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "WLS",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "the day",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "5 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "A year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "21 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Telogen",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "a year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "around 30 bucks",
            "MONEY"
          ],
          [
            "Amazon",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "almost 3 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "this weekend",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "COVID",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "last year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "3-6 months",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": false,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 8,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 3,
          "negative": 1
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 3
      },
      {
        "post_id": "j9b85u",
        "title": "I was having trouble with my hair growth for a while, I started using liquid biotin like a month ago and it’s definitely made a difference. Still need some beard help but that’s besides the point lol.",
        "clean_title": "I was having trouble with my hair growth for a while, I started using liquid biotin like a month ago and it’s definitely made a difference. Still need some beard help but that’s besides the point lol.",
        "subreddit": "Naturalhair",
        "score": 69,
        "num_comments": 9,
        "created": "2020-10-11T19:01:32+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "a month ago",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Congrats",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": false,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 7,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 0,
          "negative": 0
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 1
      },
      {
        "post_id": "c7piys",
        "title": "Does hair, skin, and nail vitamins really help hair grow more than regular multivitamins with biotin?",
        "clean_title": "Does hair, skin, and nail vitamins really help hair grow more than regular multivitamins with biotin?",
        "subreddit": "HaircareScience",
        "score": 67,
        "num_comments": 22,
        "created": "2019-07-01T07:18:33+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "entities": [],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "1,000mcg",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "13-ish",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "a crap ton",
            "QUANTITY"
          ],
          [
            "a crap ton",
            "QUANTITY"
          ],
          [
            "Nature’s Bounty Hair",
            "FAC"
          ],
          [
            "Nails",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "90%",
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            "years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": false,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 9,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 3,
          "negative": 4
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [
          [
            "000",
            "mcg"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 4
      },
      {
        "post_id": "1sl5t1",
        "title": "For those who've taken biotin, how did it affect your BODY hair?",
        "clean_title": "For those who've taken biotin, how did it affect your BODY hair?",
        "subreddit": "TheGirlSurvivalGuide",
        "score": 71,
        "num_comments": 38,
        "created": "2013-12-10T23:14:41+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "entities": [],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "10,000",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "2",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "6k",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "lemme tell",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "8 inches",
            "QUANTITY"
          ],
          [
            "approximately 10 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "3 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "6-8 weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "a year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "6 inches",
            "QUANTITY"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "about eight weeks ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "5 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "6 months to a year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "two",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "about a year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "about 4 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "a year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "about 4 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the last two or three years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "6",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "six",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "150",
            "MONEY"
          ],
          [
            "4",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "every two weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "150",
            "MONEY"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "the year",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 10,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 7,
          "negative": 5
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 6
      },
      {
        "post_id": "ff25ck",
        "title": "The slow, tedious process of the grow out! 2 1/2 years of constant trims, satin pillowcases, biotin and trying to treat my hair right ☺",
        "clean_title": "The slow, tedious process of the grow out! 2 1/2 years of constant trims, satin pillowcases, biotin and trying to treat my hair right ☺",
        "subreddit": "curlyhair",
        "score": 67,
        "num_comments": 11,
        "created": "2020-03-07T21:47:48+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [],
        "entities": [
          [
            "2 1/2 years",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Joe",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "every couple of months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "1 hour",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "this.](https://www.reddit.com",
            "LOC"
          ],
          [
            "mods](http://www.reddit.com",
            "ORG"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": false,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": false,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": false,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 5,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 1,
          "negative": 3
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 2
      },
      {
        "post_id": "8lx72o",
        "title": "If Biotin is a sham, why is there a Biotin shampoo listed in the \"Product Recommendations\" section for fine hair in the sidebar?",
        "clean_title": "If Biotin is a sham, why is there a Biotin shampoo listed in the \"Product Recommendations\" section for fine hair in the sidebar?",
        "subreddit": "HaircareScience",
        "score": 67,
        "num_comments": 17,
        "created": "2018-05-24T23:27:47+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "Biotin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "the \"Product Recommendations",
            "LAW"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "SLS",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "SLS",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "CAPB",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "DEA",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Hair",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Hair",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "almost a year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "between 2.5 and 3 feet",
            "QUANTITY"
          ],
          [
            "6 years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Dr",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Idk",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 9,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 3,
          "negative": 3
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 4
      },
      {
        "post_id": "dqrwwy",
        "title": "Do any y'all take hair vitamins? I'm getting crazy good growth from biotin, iron, and omega 369. Last hair cut was 2 weeks ago 🤣",
        "clean_title": "Do any y'all take hair vitamins? I'm getting crazy good growth from biotin, iron, and omega 369. Last hair cut was 2 weeks ago 🤣",
        "subreddit": "CurlyHairUK",
        "score": 60,
        "num_comments": 7,
        "created": "2019-11-02T22:55:15+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "omega",
          "iron",
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "omega",
          "iron",
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [],
        "entities": [
          [
            "369",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "2 weeks ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "🤣",
            "EVENT"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Holland",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "Barret",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "a week",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "4 years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Superdrug",
            "ORG"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 8,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 0,
          "negative": 2
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 2
      },
      {
        "post_id": "13j3tmr",
        "title": "Going long. Usually I trim back when I get to this length because in the past it starts looking thin, but this time around it isn’t so bad. I think it’s because I’ve been using biotin and Harry’s hair paste for texture. My goal is a foot long by the end of the year and then I’ll decide from there.",
        "clean_title": "Going long. Usually I trim back when I get to this length because in the past it starts looking thin, but this time around it isn’t so bad. I think it’s because I’ve been using biotin and Harry’s hair paste for texture. My goal is a foot long by the end of the year and then I’ll decide from there.",
        "subreddit": "beards",
        "score": 55,
        "num_comments": 8,
        "created": "2023-05-16T12:28:45+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [],
        "entities": [
          [
            "Harry",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "the end of the year",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "Wizard",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Harry",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": false,
          "product_recommendations": false,
          "progress_report": false,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": false,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 4,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 3,
          "negative": 0
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 0
      },
      {
        "post_id": "b6i6at",
        "title": "Hair thinning out. Mother mentioned Biotin, Collagen Peptides, and Peppermint Oil. Looking for a bit of assistance before buying anything.",
        "clean_title": "Hair thinning out. Mother mentioned Biotin, Collagen Peptides, and Peppermint Oil. Looking for a bit of assistance before buying anything.",
        "subreddit": "HaircareScience",
        "score": 59,
        "num_comments": 21,
        "created": "2019-03-28T12:28:36+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "biotin",
          "microneedling"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "biotin",
          "microneedling"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "Biotin, Collagen Peptides",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Peppermint Oil",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Mike",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "YouTube",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Philip b",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Minoxidil",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Super",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "2014",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "many years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the Biotin/Collagen",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "4-5 years ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Mom",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "the past year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "2%",
            "PERCENT"
          ],
          [
            "serum](https://www.amazon.com/ScalpWorks-Nourishing-Treatment-Natural-Blocker/dp",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "=gateway&sr=8-1",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "DHT",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Amazon",
            "ORG"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": false,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 9,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 7,
          "negative": 4
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 3
      },
      {
        "post_id": "fwfliy",
        "title": "25y/o, hair thinning over the years since 18y/0. Use Minoxidil/Biotin/Finasteride inconsistently for months at a time. Cut it short to lift the burden of thin hair out of mind. Still gonna use Min/Biot/Fin. I feel better about it. Here's hoping others do something similar.",
        "clean_title": "25y/o, hair thinning over the years since 18y/0. Use Minoxidil/Biotin/Finasteride inconsistently for months at a time. Cut it short to lift the burden of thin hair out of mind. Still gonna use Min/Biot/Fin. I feel better about it. Here's hoping others do something similar.",
        "subreddit": "Hairloss",
        "score": 54,
        "num_comments": 14,
        "created": "2020-04-07T06:37:17+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "fin",
          "finasteride",
          "minoxidil",
          "min"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "biotin",
          "finasteride",
          "fin",
          "min"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "finasteride"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "the years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Minoxidil/Biotin/Finasteride",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Min/Biot/Fin",
            "ORG"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "SMP",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "#1 guard",
            "MONEY"
          ],
          [
            "Asian",
            "NORP"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": false,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": false,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 7,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 1,
          "negative": 0
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 3
      },
      {
        "post_id": "2djthe",
        "title": "HIFW I realize the Biotin pills i've been taking have done wonders for my hair, but not so much for my face...",
        "clean_title": "HIFW I realize the Biotin pills i've been taking have done wonders for my hair, but not so much for my face...",
        "subreddit": "TrollXChromosomes",
        "score": 54,
        "num_comments": 26,
        "created": "2014-08-14T16:15:29+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "iron",
          "vitamins",
          "zinc"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "iron",
          "biotin",
          "vitamins",
          "zinc"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "a few days",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "a week ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "this morning",
            "TIME"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "86",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "One",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "three or so months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "daily",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "8",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "ONE",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "64",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "two a day",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Indian",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "New Delhi",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "German",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Jewish",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "First Nations",
            "ORG"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": false,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 8,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 6,
          "negative": 4
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 3
      },
      {
        "post_id": "c6or3k",
        "title": "This biotin supplement has helped me a lot with hair loss due to hypo",
        "clean_title": "This biotin supplement has helped me a lot with hair loss due to hypo",
        "subreddit": "Hypothyroidism",
        "score": 46,
        "num_comments": 22,
        "created": "2019-06-28T19:49:14+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "iron",
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "iron",
          "biotin",
          "vitamins"
        ],
        "entities": [],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "a few days",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Idk",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "a few days",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Amazon",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Amazon",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "1-2 weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "https://www.webmd.com/vitamins-and-supplements/news/20171129/fda-warns-biotin-can-distort-lab-tests](https://www.webmd.com/vitamins-and-supplements/news/20171129/fda-warns-biotin-can-distort-lab-tests",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "6 month",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "thousands",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Amazon",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "DOT",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Hair",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": false,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 9,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 3,
          "negative": 4
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 4
      },
      {
        "post_id": "11z9kmr",
        "title": "Insane hair regrowth 5 weeks on zinc, Vitamin D, Biotin (PLEASE READ CAPTIONS AND POST) - My zinc deficiency caused a receding hairline as well as diffuse miniaturization similar to DUPA",
        "clean_title": "Insane hair regrowth 5 weeks on zinc, Vitamin D, Biotin (PLEASE READ CAPTIONS AND POST) - My zinc deficiency caused a receding hairline as well as diffuse miniaturization similar to DUPA",
        "subreddit": "tressless",
        "score": 47,
        "num_comments": 37,
        "created": "2023-03-23T05:05:19+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "zinc",
          "vitamin d",
          "biotin",
          "finasteride"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "vitamin d",
          "biotin",
          "zinc"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "zinc",
          "vitamin d",
          "biotin",
          "finasteride"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "5 weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Vitamin D",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "POST",
            "ORG"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "D3",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "50-100",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "roughly 20-40",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "LOT",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "21",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "5 weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the next year",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "MPB",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "the last year and a half",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "later 5 weeks",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "Covid",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "like 3.5 years",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "10,000mcg",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "20",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "70",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "about a 1 month ago",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "15",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "4 days",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "4-6 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "daily",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "10k",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "D3",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "the last few week",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "the day",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "biotin",
            "GPE"
          ],
          [
            "k2.",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "5k",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Luc Dupanloup",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Dupa",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Belgian",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "Cubitus",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Wowser",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": false,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": true,
          "humor_meme": true,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 9,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 5,
          "negative": 1
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [
          [
            "000",
            "mcg"
          ],
          [
            "20",
            "mg"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 6
      },
      {
        "post_id": "1jvi0o0",
        "title": "Third day using the biotin beard oil I got, update I definitely  notice hair growth over my upper lip  only place I’m comfortable taking electric razor trying cut myself the rest tho I can’t feel like I fuck it up",
        "clean_title": "Third day using the biotin beard oil I got, update I definitely notice hair growth over my upper lip only place I’m comfortable taking electric razor trying cut myself the rest tho I can’t feel like I fuck it up",
        "subreddit": "beard",
        "score": 48,
        "num_comments": 7,
        "created": "2025-04-09T21:58:49+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "biotin"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "Third day",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "day 3",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "max",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Beard",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": false,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": false,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": false,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 5,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 0,
          "negative": 0
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 1
      },
      {
        "post_id": "1d6zuzw",
        "title": "PCOS hair loss - 6 months of topical minoxidil and dermarolling 0.5mm once a week (as well as biotin gummies)",
        "clean_title": "PCOS hair loss - 6 months of topical minoxidil and dermarolling 0.5mm once a week (as well as biotin gummies)",
        "subreddit": "tressless",
        "score": 44,
        "num_comments": 34,
        "created": "2024-06-03T08:51:42+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "biotin",
          "fin",
          "finasteride",
          "dermarolling",
          "minoxidil",
          "min"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "minoxidil",
          "biotin",
          "dermarolling"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "fin",
          "minoxidil",
          "min",
          "finasteride"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "6 months",
            "DATE"
          ],
          [
            "0.5mm",
            "QUANTITY"
          ],
          [
            "a week",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7540726/](https://www.ncbi.nlm.nih.gov/pmc/articles/PMC7540726/",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "SMP",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "3",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "AGA",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "fin+min",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Take Collagen",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "MSM",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "Vit B Complex",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "1000",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Redact](https://redact.dev",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Doc",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "SMP",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "one",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "three",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Scalp Micropigmentation",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Reasons",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "FACTS",
            "ORG"
          ],
          [
            "SYMBOL:::SYMBIOTE:::SIGNIFIED",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "Sweet",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "CHAR",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "69",
            "CARDINAL"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": false,
          "dosage_questions": false,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": false,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 6,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 3,
          "negative": 1
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 1
      },
      {
        "post_id": "tp6x7d",
        "title": "About 7-8 months hair regrowth min/fin/niz/derma and biotin. Hairline still the same , but overall hair looks better.",
        "clean_title": "About 7-8 months hair regrowth min/fin/niz/derma and biotin. Hairline still the same , but overall hair looks better.",
        "subreddit": "tressless",
        "score": 40,
        "num_comments": 17,
        "created": "2022-03-26T23:03:04+00:00",
        "ingredients": [
          "finasteride",
          "fin",
          "biotin",
          "min"
        ],
        "title_ingredients": [
          "fin",
          "biotin",
          "min"
        ],
        "comment_ingredients": [
          "finasteride"
        ],
        "entities": [
          [
            "About 7-8 months",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "derma",
            "PERSON"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_entities": [
          [
            "2x",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Looksgood Oral",
            "PERSON"
          ],
          [
            "1",
            "CARDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "first",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "Congrats",
            "NORP"
          ],
          [
            "6th",
            "ORDINAL"
          ],
          [
            "7th month",
            "DATE"
          ]
        ],
        "categories": {
          "ingredient_usage_patterns": true,
          "treatment_experiences": true,
          "product_recommendations": true,
          "progress_report": true,
          "side_effects": true,
          "dosage_questions": true,
          "combination_therapy": true,
          "scientific_discussion": false,
          "humor_meme": false,
          "seeking_advice": true
        },
        "category_count": 8,
        "comment_sentiment": {
          "positive": 0,
          "negative": 1
        },
        "comment_dosage_mentions": [
          [
            "1",
            "mg"
          ]
        ],
        "comment_experience_keywords": 2
      },
      {
        "post_id": "1ff5uet",
